# Anthony Hien Vu

Full Stack Web Developer Full stack web developer with a strong preference for the frontend. I also have experience in QA and DevOps (I have 2 AWS associate certifications). Wherever I work, I'm always striving to upskill everyone in my team and learn from them too. Mentoring others and working as a cohesive team is very important to me.

## Contact

### **Address**

Wentworthville, NSW, 2145

### Phone

0452668725

#### Email

avu120@gmail.com

#### **Portfolio**

https://avu120.github.io/porfolio

## GitHub

https://aithub.com/AVu120

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-hien-vu/

## **Skills**

React

Excellent

Redux

Excellent

CSS/Modules/SASS/CSS-in-JS/CSS-in-HTML

Excellent

React Testing

Excellen:

# **Work History**

2021-10 –

now

# **Senior Front End Developer**

Checkbox, Sydney, NSW

- Built new React UI in B2B application with hundreds to thousands of concurrent users.
- Fixed existing bugs.
- Made modifications to Golang APIs.

2021-03 -2021-09

## Full Stack Web Developer

oOh!media, Sydney, NSW

- Built new features into internal React & Redux applications.
- Built evergreen internal UI design system using Storybook.js. It is currently used by multiple stakeholders (e.g. designers, developers, product owners/managers, etc.) to standardize UI/UX across different web applications.
- Built new features in Node Express.js/GraphQL servers.
- Built new features in python API servers.
- Made configuration changes in AWS services like SQS, Lambda and EC2.
- Made configuration changes to Concourse CICD pipelines.

2018-08 -2021-02

# Full Stack Web Developer

Telstra, Sydney, NSW

Performed full stack development of a Telstra
enterprise web application with thousands of
internal users utilizing the MERN (MongoDB, Express,
React, Node) stack with redux. The primary feature
of this application is a catalogue of charts displaying
data from various sources. I built new features into

**Excellent AWS** Very Good **Building REST APIs** Excellent Building GraphQL APIs Good **SQL** Databases Very Good NoSQL Databases Storybook (UI Design Very Good Figma (Design/Wireframe Good

this application every day. Some examples include allowing the users to query databases from within the application, automatically schedule user-written scripts against databases, set up monitoring & alarms, and many more. The application uses a microservices architecture and is deployed on AWS.

- Go to https://avu120.github.io/portfolio/#portfolio then click on the Telstra logo to see an overview of most of my work at Telstra.
- Troubleshooted operational issues in AWS core services such as CloudWatch, EC2, ECR and DocumentDB.
- Containerized many applications using Docker.
- Configured NGINX reverse-proxies to forward requests to various servers/micro-services-in-dockercontainers.
- Wrote unit tests using Jest.js, Enzyme.js and React Testing Library.
- Wrote integration tests using ROBOT test framework.
- Set up CICD pipelines using Atlassian's Bamboo platform.
- Documented many APIs using Swagger/OpenAPI specification.
- Automated deployment of network configuration and virtual network devices using python scripts and ansible playbooks.

2017-02 -2018-05

## IT Consultant

KPMG, Sydney, NSW

- Implemented & configured Microsoft Dynamics 365
   ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) software for large multinational clients.
- Performed IT risk testing (audit).

# Languages

JavaScript

Excellent

**TypeScript** 

Excellent

# Education

2013-02 -2016-11

## **Bachelor of Science: Engineering**

Sydney University - Sydney, NSW

Python	
	Very Good
Java	
	Good
C++	
	Good

# Certifications

2021-07	AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

# 2021-03 AWS Certified Developer - Associate

# **Interests**

- Web App Performance
- Time and Space Complexity of Algorithms and Data Structures
- Frontend & Backend System Architecture
- Design
- DevOps/Cloud/Serverless
- Mentoring
- Leadership
- Sustainability
- Al/Machine-Learning

# **Hobbies**

- Ice Skating
- Cricket
- Hiking
- Running
- Reading
- Tech Meetups